To the future.
Are you the KGB officer, Nina Sergeyevna?
Yes.
Have you been providing information about Stan Beeman to the KGB?
No.
Have you been truthful with me?
Yes.
KGB officer
Let's make a break.
How are you doing?
I'm all right.
This machine is like a camera.
If you smile, does the camera know if you're happy?
No.
No, it doesn't.
It can't read your thoughts, it has no brain.
If you prefer, think of it as an insect, a wasp.
When a wasp lands on your arm, you're afraid, no?
You hold your breath and you wait for it to fly off,
and when it doesn't, what do you do?
You panic.
And when you panic, it stings you.
Perhaps it stings you because it can smell your fear,
or perhaps it stings because when you panicked,
you frightened it.
You're afraid?
And the wasp was afraid.
Chicken and egg, eh?
Do you know why the ass killed Cleopatra?
Because she moved.
Do you understand?
I must not move.
Not inside, no.
Inside, you must be still.
How do I do that?
You have to believe what you say.
You must commit to it, embrace it.
So, in order for you to drink this machine, this wasp...
Must lie to myself.
You have to lie to telegrade the truth.
Now, let's start again.